

# **Profile**

I am a graduated Front End Web Development Specialist originally from Ukraine, but currently living in Netherlands. For many years I kept the dream of becoming a developer and finally, I have achieved what I wanted. I started my coding adventure earlier in 2022, up till now. I have completed multiple projects in the past and I plan on continuing to expand my knowledge of JavaScript and React. I truly believe that productivity each day is the key to success. I continue to learn as much as possible from difference resources. I try to work hard on myself and develop through every aspect. I bring an eye for visual and user interaction design to every project. I'm always looking to learn new skills and play with new technologies. Motivated to learn, grow, and excel in data science and technology to make a positive impact on society.

# **Employment History**

#### Interpreter, Nestle (LLC Technocom), Kharkiv, Ukraine

OCTOBER 2011 - MAY 2012

Simultaneous and consecutive interpretation from/to Ukrainian / Russian and English both individually and to the large groups. Interpretation at meetings and conferences such as business negotiations, legal proceedings, and social events.

Written translation of different documents, manuals and websites.

#### Youth Counselor, Celebrity Cruises, Miami, USA

JULY 2012 - NOVEMBER 2015

Organizing and leading the youth activities, ages 3-17 years, in designated activity centers, assigned areas and throughout the cruise vessel.

#### Youth Program Manager, Celebrity Cruises, Miami, USA

AUGUST 2015 - FEBRUARY 2020

Leading the shipboard youth program's recreational, edutainment, entertainment and social programs from ages 6 months to 17 years. Supervising proper execution of the Youth Staff duties and leading the team in putting together customized and engaging programs for a wide variety of young cruise guests.

## **Education**

Bachelor, Beryslav Pedagogical College, Beryslav, Ukraine

SEPTEMBER 2002 - JULY 2006

Masters, Kherson State University, Kherson, Ukraine

SEPTEMBER 2006 - JULY 2011

Can She Code Inc, Montreal, Canada

MAY 2022 - PRESENT

#### **Details**

Hengelo

Netherlands

- +31620318484 /
- +380500554160

annabalabak15@gmail.com

#### **Skills**

CSS3

HTML5

**Bootstrap** 

**GSAP** 

Git

**JavaScript** 

React

# **Soft Skills**

Time management Communication Adaptability Problem-solving Teamwork Interpersonal skills Work ethic Attention to detail

## Languages

Ukrainian

Russian

English

Spanish

Dutch